mathsisfun.com 2002-12-06

# Maths Is Fun

* * *

  HOME

* * *

**All Pages**

A - Z Listing

**Maths Menus**

Number & Algebra

Shape, Space & Measures

Handling Data

Miscellaneous

**Maths Help**

Discussion Forum   
Online Form

**Puzzles**

Puzzles & Quizzes

**Calculators**

TI Calculators

**Computer Programs**

Winlogo Programs

**Links**

Add a link   
Maths links

**Online Shop**

Maths Books

**Contact Us**

Online Form

About Mathsisfun

|  **WWW.MATHSISFUN.COM PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.mathsisfun.com This privacy statement advises you of what information may be collected via this website and what will happen to it. 

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site   
2\. The organization collecting the information   
3\. How the information is used   
4\. With whom the information may be shared   
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under www.mathsisfun.com control   
7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   
If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact www.mathsisfun.com by email. 

**Information Collection and Use**   
www.mathsisfun.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. www.mathsisfun.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website. **Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Log Files We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Sharing We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. **Links**   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we www.mathsisfun.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. **Newsletter**   
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. **Surveys & Contests**   
From time-to-time our site or partner sites request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. www.mathsisfun.com has no control over partner site surveys and contests. Please check the privacy statement of these sites before participating. **Send a Card**   
If a user elects to use our send a card service to send an online email to a friend, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. www.mathsisfun.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site to view the online card.. www.mathsisfun.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact www.mathsisfun.com to request the removal of this information from their database. **Security**   
As www.mathsisfun.com is a free information only service and sells no products directly there is no secure server connection. At no time will www.mathsisfun.com directly request address or payment details. However, some partner sites do sell direct. Where possible it has been checked that these sites are using a secure server. Please check as www.mathsisfun.com cannot be responsible for insecure transactions from other web sites. **Choice/Opt-out**   
www.mathsisfun operates an opt in newsletter. If at any time you should wish to opt out of this newletter please send an email with the words unsubscribe in the title line and you will be removed from the mailing list. The only way to receive this email is by supplying your email address via the website. **Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.    
This site is copyright ©mathsisfun.com
